Every
time
I
come
here,
the
first
person
I
meet
is
an
immigration
officer.
Four
times
I
have
come,
four
times
I
have
met
the
same
immigration
officer,
same
Indian
officer.
immigration
officer,
when
you
land,
take
a
flight
from
India,
when
Indian
immigration
officer
says,
okay,
go.
Then
you
land
one,
another
Indian
immigration
officer
saying,
come.
Oh
brother,
mind
is
little
bent
and
this
UK
officer
is
extra
rude
also
to
Indians.
Okay,
he's
looking
at
me
passport
twice
checking,
what
do
you
checking
brother?
Then
he'll
look
at
me
and
say
what
brings
you
here?
Bulgey
legs.
Only
you
can
come
here.
Who
can
also
come
here?
It's
nice
here.